Doug Watro

DougWatro@gmail.com

DougWatro.com

631-681-0941

LANGUAGES

HTML5

CSS / SASS

JAVASCRIPT / JQUERY

JAVA

C + +

C#

SKILLS

WEB DESIGN / SEO
FULL STACK WEB DEV
SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT
UX DESIGN
ANDROID DEVELOPMENT
GAME DEVELOPMENT

SOFTWARE

ATOM / DREAMWEAVER
ANDROID STUDIO
BOOTSTRAP
MONGODB / RETHINKDB
EXPRESS / NODEJS
UNREAL ENGINE / UNITY
ADOBE CC

GOALS

Create interactive experiences that provided a service or entertain many different people.

Work together with great, passionate minds to create even greater things. Expand my knowledge and become a seasoned professional in the software, game design, or entertainment industry.

EXPERIENCE

DESIGN ASSISTANT | MAGIC SPELL STUDIOS

FEBRUARY 2014 - AUGUST 2014

Conceptualized and designed 3D game levels to be integrated within a larger game world. Work among a team of 20 to design the overall direction of the project. Designed small levels to be used in promotional material.

LEVEL DESIGNER/3D ARTIST | IGM GRAD DEPARTMENT

WINTER - SPRING 2015

Worked with a team of grad students to assist them in completing their capstone project. Acted as the sole level designer for their 3D topdown action tower defense game. Worked with other artist to model and texture assets when needed.

INDECISION BETA APP RELEASE | GOOGLE PLAY STORE

LATE 2016 - EARLY 2017

Designed, programmed, and began public beta tests of an Android App on the Google Play Store.

EDUCATION

ROCHESTER INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY 2012 - PRESENT BS | GAME DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT